{
    "id": "de6d7580dcbf4a6591f2042009a51fec",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I will call you when he ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is coming",
                "comes",
                "would come"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7d14af2967e140f39c5aa71d29c8b005"
        },
        {
            "question": "It started raining while we ..................... tennis.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are playing",
                "were playing",
                "played"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e26e8cc0f344f9095b79b2169869b95"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I have some milk before I ...................... to bed?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "am going",
                "went"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fd362bfbdc5e4a7082485e25f2030732"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. asleep while he was driving.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has fallen",
                "fell",
                "falls"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cbdae0c02f984504b309caddd3c6074e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sure I ………………….. him at the party last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "have seen",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c3318882b684e45bbf6b24867d5283e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………….. a mill in the town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "owns",
                "is owning",
                "own"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9caec14be85d4c3795150573ad9b729c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. here for the last five years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "worked",
                "was working",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1c62eb1161614c72af33179ac4baab66"
        },
        {
            "question": "He thanked me for what I …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have done",
                "had done",
                "will do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "037a0b78f1f144778fc8701683fd0f6e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t disturb me. I ..................... my homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "am doing",
                "was doing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6aca77b434464b0eac07cd297626fa50"
        },
        {
            "question": "My son ...................... to be a scientist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "is wanting",
                "has wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fefa1326bddb485eb451eadb5a11306f"
        }
    ]
}